profound.net 2011-12-01

# Privacy | Profound Networks

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.

We collect general information about your browser and ISP.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or phone number.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To send periodic emails (The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions)

### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

### Removal

If you have received a postal, email, or online offer that you believe came from us or from one of our clients, please send an email to [remove@profound.net](mailto:remove@profound.net?subject=Remove) and please provide us with as much detail about what you received: Type of offer: Email, postal, or online, the date that you received the offer, and the delivery details so that we can find the record and remove it. Consumer Phone numbers and Consumer fax numbers are not available from Marigold Technologies.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us via the information on our [Contact page](http://www.profound.net/contact/ "Contact").
